Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Constituent correspondence and services, Circa 1985-1990; Series 1
  - Downs, Thomas M., 1984; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Doyle, Pattie, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Doyle, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Draper, Guy, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Driscoll, Thomas, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Drudi, Dino, 1990; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Duarte, David W. Jr., 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Dubin, Arthur, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dubois, Elcona, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Dubose, Elcona, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dudley, Gwendolyn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Dula, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Dill, Katheryn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Dummett, Joan, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Duncan, Christina, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Dunn, Reginald, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Durall, Bob, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Dyer, Barbara, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Dyer, Samuel, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Earles, Barbara, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Easton, Joan, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Eaton, Reverend Dr. David H., 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Eberly, Donald, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Eck, Barbara, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Eckles, Katheryn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Edmonds, Barry, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Edsell, Joan, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Edwards, Elsie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Edwards, Lurline L., 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Edwards, Sylvia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Edwards, Monte, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Edwards-Price, Rose, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Eichmiller, Linda, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Einbindar, S, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Efsen, Jakob, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Egon, James, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Eliason, William, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Elliot, Kathy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Ellison, Carole, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Ellis, Grace, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Ellis, Shirley, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Elmore, Theresa, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Elwood, Nancy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Elwood, PAt, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - England, Richard, 1990; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Engler, Arthur J., 1981; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Engram, Edith, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Epsken, Sarah, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Epps, WJ, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Evans, Eloise, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Evans, John, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Eveleth, Peter, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Evins, Alan, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Falasca, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Farley, Barbara, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Farrakhan, Louis, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Farrell, Joseph, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Farrell, Laurie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Faulkner, Alice, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Feddis, Nessa, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Federico, Maureen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Feinman, Barbara, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Felder, Ellmae, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Fennell, Laura, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fenrick, Joseph Jr., 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Fenske, Tom, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ferrell, Gregory, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ferrier, Diane M., 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ferris, Deeohn, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ferris, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Fields, Carl, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1989)
  - Field, Mack, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Fields, Walter, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Filmore, Thelma, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Finis, Mamie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Firestone, Martin, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Fischer, Caron, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Fischer, Max, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Fisher, Dorothy, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Fisher, Harold, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Fisher, William, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Flam, Eli, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Fleishman, Virginia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Fleming, Diane, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Fleming, Lamont, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Flood, Brenda Mae, 1983; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Flores, Regino, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Floyd, Brenda, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Flythe, Ernestine, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Flythe, Ruth, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Fogle, Edward, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Foley, Matthew Jr., 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Fonville, Rachel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Forbes, Carlease Madison, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Forbes, Susan, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Forcey, Robert, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Forcum, Kathleen, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Ford, B, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Fors, John, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Ford, Joseph, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Ford, Michael, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Foster, Dorreen, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Fox, Elizabeth, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Frain, J. George, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - France, Roger, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Frankel, Richard, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Franklin, Azalee, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Franklin, Pamela, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Franks, Rachel, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Fredette, Judy, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Freedman, Melvin, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Freelaine, Kenneth W., 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Freeman, Consuela, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Freeman, Vinna, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - French, Lucille, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Frenkel, Ruth, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Friedman, Paul A., 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Froeb, Luke, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Fromm, Richard K., 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Frost, Alvin, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Futrell, Donna, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Funke, Odelia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Gaddis, Virginia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Gaines, Mary, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Gales, Street, 1985; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Gant, Elaine, 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Gallagher, Linda, 1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Gambrell, O'bie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Gangloff, Eric, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Garcia, Elise D., 1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Garcia, Venita, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Garnder, Charles S., 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Gardner, John W. Jr., 1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Garner, Les R. III, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Garner, Louise T., 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Gerard, Joseph, 1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gibson, Carolybn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gillis, Sherri, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gilstrap, Shawn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ginyard, Harry, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gist, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Glen, Bobby, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Glen, Robert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Godsende, Mary, 1982; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Gomez, Enrique, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Gonzalez, Joseph, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Good, Donald, 1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Goodman, Elizabeth, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Goodman, Jeffrey, 1980; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Goodwin, Mary, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Goren, Roberta, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Gould, Christopher, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Gourley, Jay, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Graham, Christie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Graham, Sheila L., 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Graham, Stephen, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Graham, Tom, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Grant, Eric, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Grant, Lyndia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Grant, Ronald, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Grant, William, 1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Grasty, Shirley, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Gray, Bernard A. Sr., 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Gray, Carolyn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Gray, Pamela, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Gray, Jesse and Selina, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Gray, Vernon, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Grays, Ron, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Grayton, Brenda, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Grayton, Gladys, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Grayton, Zachary, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Green, Harold, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Green, Gerald, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Green, Leonard, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Green, Regina/AnonymousLetter to this Office Her Behalf, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Green, Robert, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Green, W., 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Greenfield, Rita, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Greenberg, Paul, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Gregory, Julia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Griebier, Louis, 1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Griffin, Mamie, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Grillion, Mr. & Mrs. George Jacquel, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Grisby, Margaret E., M.D., 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Gruber, Jennifer L., 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Grosdidier, Marie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Hacket, Beatrice, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Hackney, Henry & Minnie, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Hagans, Dolores, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Hagans, Michele, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Hallihan, James, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Hall, David, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Hall, Helen, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Hall, Bettina, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Hallihan, James, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Hallihan, Robert, 1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Hamilton, William, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Hamilton, Kingsley, 1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Hamilton, Diane, 1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Hamlin, Bobbie, 1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Hammerman, Florence, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hampton, Ronald, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hanberry, Sandy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hancock, Gertrude, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Handy. Joseph, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hanes, Joyce, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hardy, Robin, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hardy, Willie, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hargett, Newell, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Harmon, Shawn, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Harold, Peggy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - HArper, Mildred, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Harrington, Mary, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Bryant, 1990; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Harris, James, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Harris, Timothy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Harrison, Eddie, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Harrison, Elzida, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Harrison, Phyllis, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Harrod, Dorothy, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Hart, Geroge, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hart, Helen G., 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hart, Lynn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Harting, Linda, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hartman, Robert E., 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hartridge, Alphonso, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Harvey, Louise, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Harvey, Mary, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Harvey, Samuel, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Harwood, James, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Hash, Michael, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Haskins, Robert, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Hasselman, Allen J., 1983; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hawkins, Thelma, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Hawkins, Warrenetta, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hayden, Emma, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Hayden, Marcie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Hayes, Margaret, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Haythe, Winston M., 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Hazel, Benjamin, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Hazlett, Tim, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Healy, David, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Healy, Mary, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Hechinger, John, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Hedgeman, Rudolph, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Heiliger, Donald, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Held, Barbara, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Helton, Money, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Gregory, Hemby, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Hendricks, Frances, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Henderson, Deacon Marshall, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Henry, Willard L., 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Herbert, James C., 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Herman, Christopher C., 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Herrera, Suasn, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Hester, Melissa, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Hester, Sheila, 1990; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Heydt, Erich, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Hickman, Leonard E., 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Hicks, David, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Hicks, Lilly, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Hicks, Thomas, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Higgins, Helena, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Higgins, Morgot, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Higgins, Marjorie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Hill, Annie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Hill, Kenneth, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Hill, Steven, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Hilt, Marcella, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Himelfarb, Sheldon, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Hines, Greg, 1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Hinton, Irving, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Hirsh, Loretta, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Hirshman, John, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Hoerier, Linda J., 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Hoffman, Lisa, 1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Hoffman, Susan, 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Hoffman, William, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Holland, Barbara, 1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Hollis, Barbara R., 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Holt, Evelyn, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Holt, Vernon, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Holt, Veronica, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hood, Gregory, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hopkins, Ruth, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hopkins, Shirley, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hopson, Marie, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Horigan, Brian, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Horowitz, Sandra, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Horning, Joseph, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hoston, Wanda, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hough, Evangeline, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Houston, Catherine L., 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Houston, Lenny, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Houston, Carolyn, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Howard, Jack Mr. & Mrs., 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Howell, Evelyn, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Howell, Thomas R., 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Howard, Steven, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Howerton, Kent, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Howerton, Willie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Hoyle, Fran, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Huang, Hunter, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Huette, Frederic, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Hughes, Blondine, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Hughes, Cathy, 1984; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Hughes, Charlotte, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Hull, Ronald, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Humes, Geraldine, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Humphries, Marc, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Hunt, Robert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Hunter, CA, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Hunter, Richard L., 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Hunter, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Hutcheson, Ron, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Hutchinson, Yvette, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Hwang, Gerald, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Hyde, William Mr. & Mrs., 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Hymes, Mrs. Lula E., 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Hyson, Julia, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Idahosa, Benson, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Inman, Melvin, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Irvin, Virginia, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Isham, Bill, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Isom, Joseph, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Israel, Lyne, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Ives Neighborhood Watch, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Izzo, Joseph, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Jackson, Cynthia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Jackson, Harry, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Jackson, JoAnn, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Jackson, Juanita, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Jackson, Patricia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Jackson, Reginald, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Jackson, Rubin Jr., 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Jackson, Terry, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Jackson, William, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Jacobs, Denise, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Jacobs, J. Allen, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Jacobs, Joann, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Jacobs, Judy, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Jacobs, William, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Jacobsen, Peter, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - James, Bobbie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - James, Diann, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - James, Herbert, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Jamison, Katherine, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Jasmine, Frank, 1990; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Jefferson, Deborah, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Jefferson, Wade, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Jeffries, Myna, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Jelan, Rashid, 1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Jenkins, Willie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Jenny, Lillian S., 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Jeter, James, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Joe, Barbara G., 1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - John-Gray, Carolyn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Johnson, Barbara, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Johnson, Barbara Ann, 1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Johnson, Ben, 1986; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Johnson, Betty, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Johnson, Barbara, 1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Johnson, Rosalie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Diane, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Dorothy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Debbie, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Eddie P., 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Edward, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Elizabeth, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Evelyn U., 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Helen, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Jeannie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Joseph E., 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Kenard, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Lucille L., 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Mary, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Mae, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Michael, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Mike, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Robbie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Roy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Johnson, William, 1990; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Yvonne, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Johnston, Margaret, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Jolly, Myrna, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Jones, Barbara, 1990; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Jones, Derrick and Eric, 1990; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Jones, Don, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Jones, Carla, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Jones, Elaine, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Jones, Pearl Williams Dr., 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Jones, Elsie, 1990; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Jones, Charlene, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Jones, Herbert, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Jones, Verna, 1982; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Jones, Kojo, 1990; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Jones, Steven, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Jones, Randy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Jones, Patricia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Jones, Margo, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Jones, Edna, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Jones, John, 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Jones, Georgia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Jumper, Steven, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Justice, Arthur, 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Kahn, Nina, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Kahn, Victoria, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Kaiser, Rebecca, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Kameny, Franklin, 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Kamins, Lawrence, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Karcher. Martin, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Karriem, Lydia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Kasnick, Cecelia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Kass, Nathanlee, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Katsuranis, Ann, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Kaufman, Marilyn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Kave, Edna, 1986; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Kazem, Scott N., 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Keegan, Patricia, 1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Keenan, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Keffer, Alan, 1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Kelley, Helen & Geneva, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Kelly, Marguerite, 1989; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Kelly, Scott, 1988; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kelly, Rhumetta, 1985; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Kelly, James, 1986; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Kemp, Beatrice, 1989; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Kenny, Theodora, 1989; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Keo, Mony, 1987; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)